Hello, I am Fernando and today I am going to show you what did i learn in the module 8
and I'm going to show you how to make a webpage in HTML and CSS.
This webpage will be able to play a single song.
First of all, I need to add the webpage title and I need to link a stylesheet.
Now I will add the basic things that the HTML website will have.
By the way, the webpage will have a background, a song, a pause icon and a play icon.
So now, I will add all the elements that it will have.
I have added a title for the website, a text for the website and also I have added the music icon.
And this is what we have for now.
Now that I have all the content that the webiste will have I am going to make the style of the website.
I will make a style for the container, the navigation bar, the content of webpage and the two icons that will add.
Ok, I made so ti had a  background image, i made so the navbar is on the top left
then also I changed it so that the "Music website" name is in color white in the center of the webpage.
Now for make it to work we need to add some JavaScript.
Now I will add a script where, it makes that if the song isn't playing it will play when we click the button
and if the song is already playing and we click the button it will pause the song instead of playing it again.
Now lets see if the website works propertly, this is the webpage and thats it.
Get rick rolled :)